(Spending This Moment Together)
Nice to see you all.
All right. Last week, Bokdol became a famous dog.
- Right. - My gosh.
Bokdol. Did you sleep well?
(Na Rae's new family member, Bokdol)
(Na Rae used to give him a lot of snacks.)
(Because he slept well.)
(I can't give him snacks when he wakes up? Because he slept well.)
(I clicked the video to see Bokdol, but Na Rae is so cute.)
(- Bokdol has such a cute smile. - Bokdol is smart, cute, and kind.)
(- They're both so lovable. - I hope they're happy together.)
I really appreciated comments like this.
Dog owners with brindle Jindo dogs...
- across Korea wrote... - Yes.
that people were scared when they saw brindle Jindo dogs,
but people are friendly around their dogs and thanked me.
- That's a virtuous cycle. - Bokdol was so gentle.
Bokdol had such kind eyes.
When you were dressing him,
- he was so sweet. - Right.
But you almost lost your hand.
- My gosh. - I can never dress her again.
You're actually missing out on this experience as a dog owner.
There's a certain thrill...
from the fear that you might lose your finger.
Really?
- You can't feel that thrill. - Right.
- My gosh. - It's similar.
Now that she's raising Bokdol, once the weather warms up,
dog owners should get together.
- Yes, let's do something. - Bokdol,
- Comme Des... - Yes.
- That sounds great. - It sounds amazing.
We also have Coco and Kkotbun. Let's get together.
- Call it a Dog Fun Run. - Dog Fun Run.
- Yes. - You put that together right away.
- My gosh. I knew it. Fun Run. - Of course.
Dog Fun Run.
- Gosh, this is so annoying. - I'll be there.
- Dog Fun Run sounds great. - Dog Fun Run.
(The Day Is Coming)
(Sung Hwan wakes up.)
It's Kkotbun.
(Opening up)
Come here, Kkotbun.
(Kkotbun follows Sung Hwan.)
Down.
(Down on her stomach)
Wait.
Don't eat this in one bite.
(Giving her the morning snack)
Wait.
(Bokdol's sister)
- Wait. - Gosh, she's waiting.
Oh, my. How is that possible?
Don't eat that in a hurry.
- She's basically human. - Hey.
As soon as we compliment her...
Darn.
(Excited)
Fine, eat it.
(He grabs the air conditioner filter.)
(He also takes out the blade from the fan.)
(He heads straight to the bathroom.)
Sung Hwan, it looks like you're holding the dumpling steamer.
- You're right. - They look so tasty.
- They look delicious. - There are some dumplings too.
Gosh, they look good.
My gosh.
I'm leaving...
for Kazakhstan to shoot a movie quite soon.
You already shot a movie there...
- a long time ago. - Yes. With Ju Seung.
This is nice.
(Ju Seung and Sung Hwan filmed a movie several years ago.)
That episode was fun. I liked it.
You're a celebrity representing Kazakhstan.
We'll start filming on November 30.
The shoot is for three weeks.
So cute.
- That was Kkotbun. - I thought it was a doll.
I need to use...
the AC and the fan until mid-December.
But I'm leaving soon.
Before I go abroad, I need to clean them.
That way, I'll be happy to see my filter and blade next year.
Given the timeline, I cleaned them today.
You're getting ready for winter.
- Sung Hwan keeps things clean. - He keeps them super clean.
The blade is not even that dusty.
Are you curious about what I'm doing?
Watch what I'm doing.
(Adoring her)
(He uses a toothbrush to clean the filter thoroughly.)
(To have clean filters and blade next year...)
They're all clean now.
(He finishes cleaning them under Kkotbun's watch.)
(How refreshing.)
There.
- Gosh, how neat. - That's neat.
- Right. It won't get dusty then. - You need to cover it up.
(He puts the AC filters in the well-lit balcony.)
My gosh.
I have to do this every year.
This is killing me.
How...
(He sprays the window.)
It's really cold in my house...
- because... - It's drafty in there, right?
- I mean, it gets drafty too. - That...
Because of Kkotbun, I can't keep the boiler on.
- The thing is... - She gets hot, right?
- she gets hot. - I see.
I always keep the heating system...
on the away mode or turn it up by 5°C.
So I can even see my breath.
- Whenever Ju Seung comes over, - Yes.
he tells me he can see his breath.
Insulating the window will be great during winter.
Of course. That's definitely effective.
(Carefully putting it on)
- This... - It's fascinating that...
the sheet doesn't come off.
- My gosh. - It came off.
- It came off. - It came off as soon as he said it.
It's not fascinating at all.
It's like we're jinxing everything today.
(It falls off as soon as he puts it on.)
(Confused)
(Am I doing this right?)
(Coming off)
It didn't stick.
What? Why... What's wrong with this?
- Hello. - Sir.
Yes.
Get 1 of these 2.
Right. The hardware store owner would know everything.
- You know the bubble wrap? - Yes.
I sprayed water and tried to put it up.
You must spray a lot of water.
- A lot of water? - Yes.
Then I failed to adjust the amount of water.
Right. It won't work if you spray only a little bit.
Spray water on the window, but add a bit of detergent in it.
- Detergent? - I see. Detergent.
I'll call you once I finish.
- Okay. - Okay.
(I got it.)
Just one drop?
(Adding detergent just like Sang Sik advised)
Why does he want me to add the detergent?
I think it gets sticky. Detergent might be adhesive.
Okay. That's good.
Just like Sang Sik said, I'll spray a lot of water.
My gosh. Look at this. Great.
(Trying again)
(Carefully pressing on it)
It's working now that I sprayed a lot of water.
I knew we could count on him.
- He's indeed Mr. MacGyver. - Sang Sik knew what to do.
My gosh. I knew I could count...
(I knew I could count on Mr. MacGyver of my neighborhood.)
on Mr. MacGyver of my neighborhood.
(He moves onto the next window.)
My gosh. I won't be able to see my neighbor across the street.
(Ma'am!)
Remember the thing you gave me before?
(The chili peppers weren't spicy at all.)
(The lady across the street was endlessly generous.)
She gave me sweet potatoes and corn.
(Hold on.)
I shouldn't cover up this window.
I won't be able to communicate with her.
You need to communicate with her.
I'll leave this window as it is.
(Carefully leaving the window as it is to communicate)
(He skips over a window and works on the next window.)
(He skillfully puts it on the window now.)
I didn't have any work until my shoot in Kazakhstan.
On my day off, I finished all of my chores.
You have to finish them on your day off.
(He's ready for winter now.)
(That was great.)
It suddenly got cold.
Let's see.
(Taking off)
(He suddenly takes off his sweater.)
(Walking over)
(He's stepping on the scale?)
Three months ago, I got fitted for the outfits in the movie.
I got fitted for the suit and coat. They're already tailored.
But for the past three months,
my weight peaked when it went into the triple digits.
(He was slim three months ago.)
He was so slim back then.
He slowly gained weight.
- My gosh. - Goodness.
Actually, I weigh around 112kg.
My goal is to hit 95kg.
He can't weigh that little given his build.
(Did he reach his goal?)
- My gosh. What? - What?
You didn't put the other foot down, right?
I had been on a diet for 19 days since the 1st.
(His weight goes down to a two-digit number.)
- I lost weight. - You did lose a lot of weight.
(Let me put this on.)
(Satisfied enough)
(What a relief.)
(Opening up)
Two eggs.
(Pondering after grabbing a few eggs)
(Looking in)
(A food tray?)
People use it to lose weight.
You're still trying to lose weight?
(He cuts an apple first.)
This is braised monkfish.
You already mentioned braised monkfish.
Because I get so hungry in the morning when I wake up.
Braised monkfish for breakfast...
- Right. - This is a burger.
- You love burgers too. - I'm crazy about burgers.
This is a burger patty.
There.
(But in reality, he's on a weight-loss diet.)
Gosh, soft-boiled eggs look beautiful.
Presentation matters when we eat.
My gosh. You did a great job boiling the eggs.
- Aren't those store-bought? - Six minutes and thirty seconds.
- Aren't they from a store? - No.
Six minutes and thirty seconds.
- You did a great job. - You boiled them?
- Really? - He did a great job.
- It's hard to nail boiled eggs. - That's amazing.
All right.
(He grabs the food tray and trudges over.)
(A completely healthy meal with black soybean soup)
(Looking simple)
Wait. It's the lady.
The lady...
(Rushing over as he's happy to see her)
- Ma'am! - You startled me.
What are you doing?
I'm making kimchi.
You won't give me any?
Seriously. That lady... You're not looking up...
- on the rooftop, right? - You won't give me any?
- She always shows up around now. - Right.
She's busy. She went back in.
She's like a fairy.
She's like a character in games. What do you call it? NPX?
I wonder what she's doing.
(I should just eat my meal.)
She went back in so fast.
My gosh.
- As soon as you turn on the TV... - That happens to me too.
You'll watch that when you're on a diet?
When I watch during my meals, it feels like...
- I'm eating the same food. - Right.
(Having a bite while pretending to eat the same food)
(You should eat some too.)
(Smacking his lips)
He's eating slowly.
My gosh, ramyeon.
Ramyeon looks so good.
(Looking appetizing)
- What a good way to break the egg. - My gosh.
The last time I ate ramyeon was...
three weeks ago.
(Swallowing hard)
(Salivating)
Gosh, that looks crazy good.
The lady knows how to present the food beautifully.
(Eating vicariously through the eating show)
(Sighing)
(Oh, poor me.)
Have some too.
- The apple must taste like nothing. - You must overcome this.
(He used to eat everything he wanted.)
I remember that day.
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
It's driving me crazy.
(I'm so happy.)
- Your expressions are different. - They're very different.
Right.
- Gosh, that looks good. - Apples are tasty now.
But I wanted ramyeon...
or food with a lot of seasoning in the morning.
(Looking dejected)
Smile when you eat.
- Are you crying? - He'll cry soon.
(He soothes his bitter heart with the soybean soup.)
I'm done too. I finished my meal.
He must feel so empty inside.
I'm done.
Wait.
- Today... - I bet he's ordering food.
He really is.
- I was wrong. - He's...
- I didn't know you kept a log. - Okay. It got into the 90s today.
It's 99.8kg.
(Recording his weight on his phone)
My gosh. On November 1,
my weight was 109.4kg.
I lost exactly 10kg within 19 days.
But I don't look so different after this weight loss.
(Feeling upset)
Tomorrow is the 20th.
(His meals for tomorrow are already set.)
A Korean buffet restaurant.
On the 24th, I can have curry rice with scallop.
You're having that on the 24th.
It's an app that helps me lose weight.
It records breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
But I didn't initially use it for my diet.
I usually write down my meals for the week.
The joy of my week...
comes from going to these restaurants.
So I write down what I'm going to eat.
I started writing down my meal plans since 2010...
when I checked the log.
- You kept the log for a long time. - Why do you keep the log?
But why do you look like that?
- This... - "Why do you look like that?"
- "Why do you look like that?" - That app isn't for diet tracking.
I think about what I'm going to eat next week.
- My meals for tomorrow. - He even has meal plans...
for next month.
Sung Hwan showed it to me yesterday at Jang Woo's wedding.
He already planned his meals for the next two months.
- Like what he's going to eat? - Yes.
Ask him to show you his calendar later.
That sounds like a calendar for a drama shoot.
- Two months... - Seriously.
Even housewives won't be able to plan that far ahead.
That's impressive.
Year 2013. Gosh, there it is.
- I got goosebumps too. - My goodness.
You wrote down everything you ate.
"Vegetable bibimbap with instant rice and eggs."
- "Half an apple, cheese..." - "Failed to rebuild my body."
Hold on. At 5:30pm, he had...
- "Failed to rebuild my body." - beer, fried chicken,
sausages, and pizza.
- Rebuild... - You're not a cyborg.
Why did you write it like that?
Have you ever succeeded?
(Succeeded to rebuild my body)
- What is this? - "Succeeded to rebuild my body."
- You succeeded? - Yes, I did.
- You had rice balls, spicy pork, - Spicy pork and Pikachu cutlet...
- Pikachu cutlet, - Pikachu cutlet?
chicken and sundae on a stick.
That's about working out.
It's not about losing weight.
- I did CrossFit. It's so intense. - I guess your workout...
- was intense. - It's about that.
(Failed to follow the meal plan and work out)
Gosh, your weight was 93kg.
You lost a lot of weight.
I'm good at losing weight.
(Weight: 93kg)
Kkotbun, we should go out too. Come here.
Let's go. My gosh. Let's go to your favorite spot.
All right.
(Putting on a leash for safety)
Let's go.
- She has her go-to walking route? - Yes.
She only goes there?
- No. We have a lot of routes. - What's this?
- I see. You do. - But we go there most frequently.
(Sung Hwan is going somewhere with Kkotbun.)
(Singing)
(Where are we going?)
(Driving past the bustling city)
(His car heads toward the suburbs.)
(He parks his car in a secluded corner.)
I love you
(Are we here?)
How nice.
All right.
(He gets out of the car with Kkotbun.)
My gosh. Let me put on a leash before we go.
(He trudges along with the leash.)
(Barking)
(Saying hello to a dog)
The dog looks like Comme Des.
Let's go.
(Kkotbun, let's walk now.)
(Excited)
Let's go.
Let's go and meet your favorite lady.
Your friends are here.
My gosh, hello.
Oh, my.
Some dogs are happy to interact.
(A dog comes out to say hello to Kkotbun.)
Hello.
(Showing interest)
Pretty soon, Kkotbun and I...
will have to be apart briefly.
I love coming to this park for a reason.
To come here, I have to drive for 20 minutes.
But she can run freely at this park.
- The park is set up nicely. - I'd love to take Bokdol there.
This park is great.
Gosh, Bokdol will have so much fun there.
The space is separated for small and large dogs.
So I bring her here often.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
Hello. Could you scan her?
- Scan what? - The identification chip...
on her back.
- Did you get one for Bokdol? - Right.
- You need that. - Yes, he got his chip.
Hello.
- Hello. - He's going to the food truck.
- I guess you've been there often. - I go there often.
I'll take this one. Kkotbun likes it.
I'd like a cup of yuzu tea.
Yuzu tea?
(She can't believe her ears.)
I've been on a diet lately.
I'd like yuzu tea and a bit of the fishcake soup.
- Sure. You got it. - Okay.
- What's my total? - It's 7.5 dollars.
It's 7.5 dollars.
I'll give you eight dollars...
- including the fishcake soup. - My gosh.
- It's okay. - Take eight dollars.
By the way, people can eat this too, right?
- Of course. - Yes.
She makes such tasty treats. I'm serious.
- Sweet potatoes? - Yes.
(Humming)
I'm on a diet, but this tastes so good.
- Of course. - Gosh.
That was the tastiest food I had since breakfast that day.
You're stealing her food now that you're on a diet.
You might even end up eating dog food later.
(Joking)
(Warm yuzu tea and fishcake soup are served.)
- Thanks. I'll put them here. - Okay.
(He enters the playground for medium-sized and small dogs.)
My gosh. You look handsome.
(Securing the door)
- This park looks amazing. - This place is great.
I didn't know about this park.
Come here, Kkotbun.
(He puts down Kkotbun in the playground.)
- How nice. - She must be so excited.
- Wait. - She seems interested in Kkotbun.
She wants to say hello.
(The dogs begin sizing up each other out of curiosity.)
(Barking)
What's wrong? Be nice to your friend.
- Kkotbun doesn't want to. - Really?
(Kkotbun, let's have some snacks.)
(Fueling up with the sweet potato snack)
(Kkotbun is running excitedly after the energy boost.)
How adorable.
So many puppies are coming in all of a sudden.
(Kkotbun's buddies flood in.)
Kkotbun, so many of your buddies are here.
Gosh, one of them is wearing sunglasses.
(A cool dog with sunglasses enters.)
- What? - What a cool dog.
- That's a cool dog. - They all look so cool.
Come here. My gosh, look at you. You're excited.
(Other dogs flock to him too.)
- Hey. - My gosh.
- Come here. - She won't let them come near you?
- Is she jealous? - That's part of the reason too.
- She's jealous. - She's jealous.
(Exploding with jealousy)
She's jealous.
Gosh, come here. Let's have some snacks.
(Another dog runs toward him.)
Gosh. Let's have some snacks.
(Another puppy is in Sung Hwan's arms.)
- What? - Come here.
(Feeling threatened right away)
(Who are you looking at?)
My gosh.
(Go away!)
Gosh, she's jealous.
- Of course. - Come here.
Come here.
(Kkotbun won't leave Sung Hwan's side.)
(The unwelcome guest keeps on teasing.)
But she won't bite the other dog.
- She only threatens the dog. - Right, she's all bark and no bite.
When you look at her tail, she's not trying to attack the dog.
(I'm going to protect Sung Hwan!)
Come here.
Are you done playing?
(Quickly dashing over to Sung Hwan's side)
Try to get along with other dogs.
(He holds another puppy in his arms.)
You're quite chubby.
(Staring)
- My gosh. - She's jealous.
Why do you keep holding other dogs?
Do you eat pork belly before going to sleep?
(I'm the only dog he can hold in his arms.)
How beautiful.
(Burning with jealousy)
My goodness.
- Oh, no. Look at her. - She's going away.
- She's sulking. - She's upset.
This isn't right.
- Gosh, she's sulking. - Hey.
(Kkotbun is sulking hard.)
(He's looking for Kkotbun after playing with another dog.)
My gosh, that dog...
Kkotbun.
(Pouting)
Come here.
(Heading over)
Come here, Kkotbun. Let me check your belly.
Come here, Kkotbun.
- Gosh, you look so dirty. - She does look dirty.
My gosh. Seriously. Look at you.
Touching your belly after the other dog's belly...
I shouldn't touch a lady's belly?
She doesn't like it when you touch her belly.
You know? You're a beautiful dog.
Look at you.
(Sung Hwan hugs her tightly in his arms.)
(Patting)
- Let's see. - Then...
who's going to look after Kkotbun for three weeks when you're away?
I'm considering to ask my parents to look after her.
Or I could ask her kindergarten since she already goes there.
She wants to play with her friends more.
I'm trying to decide what to do.
I'm considering the dog hotel too...
because they send me photos...
- and videos throughout the stay. - Right.
- That and there are other dogs. - Right.
- Right. - They have a good system.
I'm still worried to be apart from her. I already feel...
I don't have children, but it feels like I'm raising a kid.
- Do you already feel emotional? - Yes.
Yes, I do.
- He does look sad. - Yes.
The last time he went away, it was about a month.
So he cried when he saw her again.
- Right. - He might cry again.
(He cried when he saw Kkotbun after a month.)
(Kkotbun is always so lovable.)
(Half asleep)
Let's go.
Bye.
It tasted great, ma'am.
- Did you have fun? - Yes. My gosh, we had so much fun.
Bye.
- Okay. Bye. - Bye.
(Let's come back next time, Kkotbun.)
(They come back home after a fun day.)
(Groaning)
- She's in his arms. - Gosh.
She's sleepy.
She's already half asleep.
(Grunting)
- Hey. - I also get tired after the trip.
I'm exhausted too, Kkotbun.
Gosh, how will I wash you?
- You have to wash her? - I need to wash you.
(He takes off his jacket first.)
(Sung Hwan sits down.)
Kkotbun.
You know what we're doing with the newspaper on the floor.
You'll groom her?
Gosh, she hates it.
Dogs know everything.
Come here, Kkotbun.
Come. Hurry, Kkotbun.
Hurry.
(I got you.)
- We don't have much time today. - How cute.
What a good girl.
Like this.
- I'm going to... - You'll cut it just like that?
- Really? My gosh. - Gosh.
- You must check the style. Gosh. - Come on.
- I've been doing this for a decade. - Really?
Okay.
My gosh. You look great.
Whether I leave her with my parents or at the dog hotel,
she must look neat.
Kkotbun, you're behaving so well. Oh, my.
You're starting to look more beautiful.
- You've done that a lot. - Gosh, of course.
Kkotbun is such a gentle dog.
Here comes the clipper.
Gosh, I can't even attempt to do that.
- I can't even try using that. - My gosh.
She's usually groomed by a professional,
but I trim around her eyes and nose from time to time.
- For hygiene purposes? - That's all I do. Yes.
I need to take good care of you while I'm in Korea.
Here it comes again.
- I knew it. - It's starting.
- My gosh. - She doesn't like that.
So how were the other puppies today?
(You adored only other dogs. I'm upset.)
- But she's still gentle. - That's it.
She only growled. How nice of her.
I see, Kkotbun. That's how you felt.
That's my skill.
- You have to baby her. - You're almost done.
She's so cute.
(His grooming skills are smooth.)
Well done.
My gosh. Who's this?
(Her beauty just leveled up.)
Isn't it nice to get your hair trimmed?
Kkotbun, listen. Here's the thing.
- Dogs are our forever friends. - Yes, that's right.
Let's go and take a half-body bath which you love.
She loves doing half-body baths?
She doesn't like full-body baths, but she likes half-body baths.
- Gosh, really? - Yes.
- Her body must ache too. - Yes.
We can wash ourselves.
Dogs don't seem to like it because we have to do it for them.
- Would you like it if I washed you? - Right. They don't like it.
- What are you talking about? - What are you saying?
He's not a dog.
If it's done by a professional, she might like it.
Why is he comparing Ju Seung to a dog?
- I'm sorry. - He's a human.
(I'm sorry, Ju Seung.)
(Gushing out)
Come here, Kkotbun. Hurry.
Come here. Hurry up.
(Lifting her)
Gosh. It's nice and warm.
- Once their coat gets wet, - How nice.
- their true body shape shows. - Gosh, how nice.
How nice. Isn't it nice?
It can't be too hot or too cold.
The perfect temperature is about 38°C.
Then I add the bath powder for bubbles...
which I don't even use for myself.
- You have to add that. - That's nice.
- You must add that. - I put in vegan shampoo too.
I add everything and give her a half-body bath.
(Snoring)
I'll play your favorite music.
Apparently, classical music is good for the dogs.
- Dogs like it. - I learned that.
How nice.
Go to sleep.
Oh, my.
(Blinking)
- You see the shape of her body. - She's sleepy.
Dogs really do that.
(Gosh, Kkotbun.)
She's sleepy.
(You're sleepy.)
She looks like she has gone through a breakup.
(My Kkotbun)
- I think she's sleeping. - She's very tired.
Sung Hwan, if Kkotbun likes the half bath,
you should put a plushie that comes up to here.
Then she'll lean on it and nap for a while.
My goodness. That's a great tip.
Shall we wash up, Kkotbun? Let's wash up.
(He massages Kkotbun in an experienced way.)
She's so tiny.
- How cute. She's so tiny. - That's right.
Hey, now...
(Shaking off water)
- Hey, now... - It's refreshing.
(It's understandable.)
- It can't be helped. - Dog mist.
You need to be prepared to get wet.
It'll take forever to dry you off.
All right.
Kkotbun, I'm exhausted too.
(I'm exhausted.)
Oh, my,
(Groaning)
Okay.
(You shouldn't catch a cold.)
Gosh, Kkotbun.
Let's get dried up. Come here.
The wind is strong, so you'll get dried up in no time.
(Drying)
Kkotbun is staying still.
You're getting dried up in no time since the wind is strong.
You're becoming fluffy.
It's very convenient since the hair dryer can stand.
You got dried up in no time thanks to this product.
(Fluffy)
(He sprays some mist.)
All done.
- Kkotbun is gentle. - I'm jealous.
I'll wash up and head out.
- Kkotbun, I'll play some music. - That's right.
- Let's go. - She's clean.
- She's fluffy. - She's looking at her dad only.
I'll be back.
I'm running late.
(Sung Hwan plays the music and heads out hurriedly.)
Let's go. I'll be back, Kkotbun.
(Pressing)
They'll scold me for being late.
- I need to hurry up. - Where is he going?
- Are those presents? - Let's go.
Gosh, it smells nice.
- The budae jjigae place looks good. - I love budae jjigae.
Budae jjigae is tasty.
(Singing)
I'm here.
(Sung Hwan enters a place.)
Where is he going?
- Hello. - Hello.
- Oysters. - Yellowtail.
- Crabs. - My goodness.
Yellowtail.
They're in season.
Mom.
- "Mom?" - It must be his mom.
Hey, you didn't give me a single call.
- Yes, I did. - You just left instant messages.
- I called you last time. - What?
She's Ju Seung's mom.
What is my mom doing there?
Hey, you didn't give me a single call.
- Yes, I did. - You just left instant messages.
- I called you last time. - What?
She's Ju Seung's mom.
I brought you a present for you.
I went there to see Ms. Jeon-ja Gwi Sim.
(What's your mother's name?)
(It's Jeon-ja Gwi Sim-ja.)
(Shouldn't you say, "Jeon Gwi-ja Sim-ja?")
(He made it sound like "Electronic ghost.")
- Jeon-ja Gwi Sim. - Ms. Jeon-ja Gwi Sim.
You know, I want to say something.
- Just don't. - It has been many years...
since I've said her name.
I wondered what "Jeon-ja Gwi Sim" meant.
- What's "Jeon-ja Gwi Sim?" - It sounded like a modern ghost.
I thought her last name had two syllables like Namkoong.
- Jeon-ja. - Same here.
The kind of last names only 1 or 2 people have in Korea.
I knew her name,
so I was like, "What? Did she change her name?"
To Jeon-ja Gwi Sim?
That's why people call her Madame Digital these days.
Madame Digital.
- That's right. - Madame Digital sounds hip.
(Madame Digital is close to Sung Hwan, Ju Seung's best friend.)
(Sung Hwan, Gwi Sim, Ju Seung)
Sung Hwan was so skinny.
- Mom was young back then. - I know.
Of course, we became close through Ju Seung.
Mom is completely open-minded.
She's practically a friend of mine.
There's nothing we don't talk about.
We're friends who talk about anything and everything.
That's incredible.
I'm close to Ju Seung's mom...
because her place was a hideout when Ju Seung lived with her.
When we had 1 or 2 rounds of eating and drinking,
we went to Mom's place for the third round.
Then we talked together.
- How nice. - Would anyone else have...
his or her friend's mom as a drinking buddy?
- Seriously. - It's rare.
- It's rare. - It's so fascinating.
- It's rare indeed. - So...
if Ju Seung was busy,
- he didn't come. - It really was a hideout.
If I was busy, I didn't come.
I think it'll be fun.
It'll be great.
- What? - Here.
- Your feet... - Gloves?
- Your feet can get cold. They're... - They're so thick.
touchscreen-friendly.
They're so thick. How are they touchscreen-friendly?
Are those presents?
Mom made me a packed meal.
I remember that.
You should put on the gloves.
- Are they nice? - Of course.
I bought you something cheap.
Gosh, you didn't need to get me anything.
- I'll get you things. - I put them on.
What do you think?
- They're warm. - They look good on you.
Did you order something?
(Shall we order something?)
- No, I didn't. No one was here. - Then...
Sir.
Grilled gizzard shads, grilled shrimp, and yellowtail.
- My goodness. - And...
- let's eat steamed oysters. - You must eat steamed oysters.
- Can you eat all of those dishes? - We'll order those dishes.
- Various dishes. - Yes.
I'm not worried because you're here.
I met my goal weight of 97kg to 99kg today,
so I went there to enjoy my cheat day.
- So I ordered various dishes. - A cheat day.
- Is today a cheat day? - A light breakfast will be useless.
Wait. You had an apple...
- for breakfast. - Yes.
I need to have one proper meal a day.
You have a cheat day 365 days a year.
That's why I don't yo-yo much.
That's because you don't lose weight.
You don't go on a diet.
You only yo-yo when you lose weight.
And Mom,
- do you want soju? - What?
- I want Chum Churum. - Chum Churum.
Mom likes soju.
Why would you drink when there's no food?
You like drinking on an empty stomach.
Drinking on an empty stomach...
- is nice indeed. - Her drinking method is intense.
- You have Kim Hae Sook's hair. - I didn't touch my hair.
It isn't a wig, is it?
Of course not.
(Take a look.)
That motorcycle behind her looks like hers.
- Does she ride a motorcycle? - Does she ride a motorcycle?
It's good to see you after a long while.
It's a heartwarming sight.
- Will you be there for a month? - Three weeks.
Apparently, it's insanely cold there.
So I got a vest for you...
after much consideration.
That's right. She bought it for you.
- Try it on. - I love it.
- Hey, the color... - It's pretty.
Foreigners come to Korea...
- and buy it these days. - That's right.
- That's right. - Grandma's vest.
It was too small for me, so...
No.
See?
I just need to button the bottom one.
(It fits perfectly.)
(What?)
- Oh, my. Hold on. - That startled me.
Mom, peel them for me.
I can peel them when they're cooked.
Hey, how about this?
I bought socks for Kazakhstan.
- They're new. - I needed socks.
She gave me quality socks.
This is... I don't know if it's big enough for you.
What is it?
Gosh, I was going to buy it.
- Oh, my. - It suits him.
I can't believe you came at this time.
- You came as soon as I put it on. - Ju Seung?
- Hello. - Ju Seung?
- It's a woman. - It isn't Ju Seung.
- I put it on just now. - Sung Hwan,
- you should go to Mongolia. - What?
- What? - Who is she?
She's Actor Lee Se Na.
I got to know her through Ju Seung.
We've become best friends.
She's a friend who's like my younger sister.
What's Lee Se Na's relationship to the group?
She was in a play with me.
- Why aren't you there? - Seriously.
- Why aren't you there? - They're hanging out without you.
We go back 15 years. We're the closest.
Why didn't you join them?
I had a schedule the day before.
It ended so late that I couldn't join them.
- My goodness. - That's too bad.
We contacted him, but...
- You contacted him, right? - Of course.
They contacted me.
This group is like that.
If some people can't come, we hang out without them.
- That way, we hang out more often. - Okay.
Mom got this for me since I was going to Kazakhstan.
Mom, I'll use it well.
Mom and Se Na meet up very often.
- By themselves. - They're very close.
Such a relationship begins when the mom approaches first.
I'll use it well.
- Se Na. - Yes?
- Here. - What's that?
He brought a present.
- They're so cute. - Isn't the color nice?
- You can use your phone with them. - The texture is so nice.
This is perfect.
You arrived just when the shrimp got cooked.
Hey, A Ran.
- A Ran came as well. - Hello.
Hello, Ma'am.
(Another friend comes.)
Her name is A Ran.
She's Ju Seung's close friend who lived in the same neighborhood.
Everyone came except for Ju Seung.
- What's this? - We lived in the same neighborhood.
(What's this?)
Ju Seung brought this group of friends together,
but we've gotten close on our own since then.
(A Ran, Ju Seung's mom, Sung Hwan)
Ju Seung isn't in the photo.
I'm the driver.
We're totally like a family.
He brought their worlds together and stepped out.
- I have something for A Ran. - What is it?
- Here. - Thank you.
They're matching gloves. They have the same pair.
I pushed the stroller every day without gloves.
- Really? - My hands were so cold.
I was going to buy gloves.
- It has been so long, A Ran. - I know. Have you been well?
- She lives far away. - Really?
You've gotten prettier.
It's because she has gotten her hair done.
(It's because she has changed her hairstyle.)
Hold on. This is yellowtail.
It looks tasty.
(Yellowtail sashimi looks good since it's in season.)
- My goodness. - It looks tasty.
- I love shrimp so much. - Do you want it?
(There are grilled gizzard shads as well.)
- Thank you. - He picked the best dishes.
Those are gizzard shads.
Are those gizzard shads?
Mom, open wide.
This is incredible.
- My goodness. - Open wide.
How is it?
It doesn't happen every day.
You're so good to her.
I don't know why...
- close friends always live far. - I know. It's always like that.
I feel so lonely.
- We miss each other at times. - I know.
We used to meet up spontaneously.
What's funny is that we've become close thanks to Ju Seung...
and traveled together.
But Ju Seung isn't here right now.
- Ju Seung is busy. - Ju Seung is busy.
- Do you know why? - What?
Do you know why Ju Seung can't run well?
- He can't run well? - What does she mean?
(What is she going to say?)
- He has no athletic abilities. - No.
When he runs...
- Don't say that he's bow-legged. - I say this all the time.
- He's out-toed when he runs. - Really?
- She's right. - She's right.
She's right.
(Mom, why are you saying that over there?)
Other people run like this,
but he runs like this. That's why he's slow.
(Mom, you're so funny.)
- You know, - It's tasty.
- yellowtail is tasty. - Yes.
It's in season.
Yellowtail goes well with dried laver.
- It's fatty. - This kind of food...
doesn't make you gain weight even if you eat a lot.
It's so good.
Seasonal food is the best.
- It looks tasty. - It's the best.
I'll give you one.
My goodness. Steamed oysters are good.
(He feels dizzy.)
- Time passes fast. - They're steamed oysters.
My goodness.
It's so big.
(Mom should try tasty food first.)
- Try this oyster. - It looks so tasty.
(Since I'm on a diet, you should eat a lot in my stead.)
(Happy)
Se Ra and A Ran...
Hey, we've known each other for many years.
- We go way back. - When...
When I lived with Ju Seung,
I was in my 30s.
(It was about 8 years ago.)
I've been having this thought.
I feel bad about saying this in front of Mom,
but time...
Don't act up.
(Don't act up in front of me.)
- "Don't act up." - "Don't act up."
I didn't know that your legs were short.
But you kept bringing it up.
It's a different topic.
It's totally like quantum mechanics.
The topic changes constantly.
(Hey, do you brush...)
(your teeth like this or this?)
(Do you do it horizontally or vertically?)
(The master of the quantum mechanics speech)
Your legs do look a bit short.
- His shoulders are broad. - It's because his torso is big.
He has Popeye's torso,
- so his legs look short. - Wait.
Are you criticizing me or complimenting me?
I've never seen a 180cm-tall man with short legs.
Look closely. Sung Hwan...
- Don't look closely. - looks very cute in this area.
- Now comes the compliments. - Compliments.
He's handsome.
Why does he look like that on TV?
It's so funny.
(Her quantum mechanics speech is unpredictable.)
- Come on. - My goodness.
I'll eat like this today.
- That's too much. - But if I do this,
my eyesight in the right eye will become bad.
It's like watching the neighboring table in a pub.
Mom.
I've been stressed out recently,
but meeting up with you guys and chatting makes me feel better.
- It's fun. - Same here.
I was under a lot of stress.
- Were you? - Yes.
Why?
- When you're past the mid-60s... - It's the hormones.
- That's right. - You think,
"I haven't achieved much until I reached this age."
Things worsen when children get married.
- That's right. - Yes.
Mom, you have Ju Seung and us.
There are times I feel that way due to my age.
- I see. - It's natural.
When things get tough, call me.
When Mom called me a few days ago,
we talked for an hour.
She called me when I was walking my dog.
We talked for an hour. It was so much fun.
- We talked about the past. - That's right.
- Mom. - Time passes fast.
It's so nice.
Ju Seung must be happy...
- to have friends like them. - That's right.
I feel so comfortable when we meet up like that.
- That's right. - I'm so thankful for everyone.
I'd absolutely love it...
- if my friends did that. - That's right.
Peel it for me.
(Amicable)
- How are the four of them so close? - I know.
It means Ju Seung's mom has a great personality.
- That's right. - Yes.
It's only possible when she opens up her mind.
One, two, three.
Be healthy.
My hair is like this.
It's nice.
There are people who make you happy...
- even when you see their backs. - It's so nice.
I couldn't wait to talk to these people.
Today's gathering was like that.
- It's so nice. - We have different wavelengths.
I don't know what we're talking about.
But we always get excited...
and happy. The gathering was like that.
I forgot to give you this earlier.
Take care of yourself when you go there.
- Are those masks? - You can put...
wet cotton inside those masks.
- I must be crazy. - I haven't seen them before.
- Why? - Why? Are you tearing up?
Why?
- Are you crying? - Cry!
- Now is the chance. - Sung Hwan cries a lot these days.
- My mom takes photos right away. - She takes photos right away.
- My mom takes photos right away. - Why are you crying about...
- her present? - I must be crazy.
I can't believe him.
Turning 40 made me that way.
Stop it.
- No. - Wink like nothing happened.
There you go, Sung Hwan.
That's good.
- How nice. - I miss them.
(I Live Alone)
Let's welcome the main character of the Rainbow Live.
It's the big project of I Live Alone...
that's back after 2 years and 8 months.
Introducing the Rainbow Friends, IRF.
(Introducing the Rainbow Friends)
I introduced Hae Jun...
- and KEY introduced Chang Sub. - Yes.
- This is the third one. - Who will introduce a friend?
Today, KEY will introduce a friend.
- The second friend. - KEY's friend.
Let me give you a hint.
You saw this person in my daily life.
- Was this person on the show? - Yes, you saw this person.
In a recent drama, he played an ex-boyfriend...
who made everyone angry.
- Who is he? - Yes.
He is an actor who is my close friend.
Seo Bum June, welcome.
The housewarming party.
- Hey. - Hello.
It's so strange to see you like this.
- He's a handsome man. - He's handsome.
- Seriously. - Hello.
("Would You Marry Me?" ranked 1st in terms of viewers' ratings...)
(among shows that aired in the same time slot.)
(He played a loser ex-boyfriend in the drama...)
(an became the nation's pretty garbage.)
(With the acting career he has built up,)
(the rising star won the Newcomer Award...)
(at both SBS and KBS in 2024.)
(Actor Seo Bum June)
Hey.
- Welcome. - Hello.
It's so strange to see you like this.
- He looks so pretty. - Nice to meet you.
- He has lost more weight. - Welcome.
- All right. - He's handsome.
How does he look so pretty?
Thank you.
He's handsome.
Please say hello to the viewers.
Hello, I'm Actor Seo Bum June.
- It's nice to meet you. - Yes.
Bum June appeared on the show when KEY had a housewarming party.
- He ate with so much gusto. - That's right. He eats a lot.
(It was nice to see them eat well. They were like the dad and the son.)
(Bum June ate as well as Se Yoon.)
- I absolutely love to eat. - Really?
- Where does it all go? - Seriously.
I work out a lot.
That's the difference.
- I see. - I see.
I wanted to meet everyone.
- Really? - Yes.
Whom did you want to meet the most? Exclude KEY.
- I wanted to meet everyone, but... - Choose one.
That's right.
I wanted to meet...
the Palm Oil Family members.
My goodness.
(Cheering)
- That's his taste. - Yes.
- Palm Oil Family needs a looker. - That's right.
- We have an opening. - Really?
- Yes. - Just in time.
- He got married yesterday. - We had an opening yesterday.
We had an opening yesterday. Oh, my.
Jang Woo was the looker of the group.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
Welcome. We always welcome you.
- Thank you. - All right.
We'll give you the application form.
- Okay. - Yes.
You can fill it up during the fun run.
- Fun run, my foot. - Fun run.
It's a slave contract.
All contracts rolled into one. For goodness' sake.
- It's nice. - My goodness.
(He feels a bit worried.)
(The Long-Awaited)
(It's pitch dark in the room.)
Gosh, I can't watch.
- It hasn't even started. - Gosh.
(He sleeps without any movement in the dark.)
(Rushing over)
- Gosh! - Dogs always do that.
- Right? - They're always like that.
Did you sleep well, Monde?
(Still half-awake)
This is Monde, the dog I live with.
- How old is Monde? - Monde is two.
- Monde is still a baby. - Monde is still a baby.
(Stretching)
(Peeking)
Hello. I've lived alone for nine years.
My name is Seo Bum June and I'm an actor.
It's great to see you all.
It feels strange to see you like this.
It's the same for me.
He looks like ZICO.
- Right. - He looks like ZICO.
I often hear that I look like you.
- I'm sorry about that. - No. I feel grateful.
(The CODE KUNST lookalike puts on his glasses.)
(Getting up)
(He gets up early at 6:05am without an alarm.)
It's 6am?
Why did he wake up so early...
- at that age? - Gosh.
I got up at 6am as I slept at 11pm the night before.
Do you sleep at 11pm?
It has become a sort of pattern for me.
(He heads out to the living room as soon as he gets up.)
(It's my house!)
(Welcome to Bum June's house.)
It's neat.
I like things that are simple, neat, and white.
I went around to look for each piece of furniture.
(The medicine containers are placed on the wall.)
(The cleaning tools are placed in the gaps.)
He must've been always great at keeping things organized.
He's always neat.
(The closets are organized neatly as well.)
(The bedroom is flawless as well.)
(Stylish items are placed around the house as well.)
There are his awards.
(The honorable moments are always kept close to him.)
(A house that welcomes him with awards and dinosaurs)
Hey, Monde.
(Plopping down)
- Gosh. - The smell of those cute paws.
(He charges up with the smell of Monde's paws.)
I should brush my teeth, Monde.
(Getting up)
(He rinses his mouth first with the mouthwash.)
(He then brushes his teeth.)
(Monde greets Wilson.)
(That feels refreshing.)
I'll give you some water.
(He fills Monde's bowl.)
Wait.
I understand now.
I have to feed my baby even if I don't get to eat.
- Right. - Right.
You still eat.
(A warm bowl dried pollack soup)
I have to feed myself as well.
How dare you try to pretend not to eat?
(He opens up the fridge.)
(Shall I have some breakfast as well?)
(He places a piece of bread into the air fryer.)
(Get toasted nicely.)
(He gets out a mysterious container out of the fridge.)
- What is that? - Monde.
- It's bulgogi. - I see.
You're having bulgogi with bread?
(Sizzling)
Gosh, this is insane.
(The cheese falls like snow.)
When I get done with a project,
I tend to eat whatever I want to for a day.
It isn't a complete cheat day.
It's a half-cheat day today.
(The first dish is the cheese bulgogi sandwich.)
When I have a cheat day,
I plan what to have the day before.
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
Even the desserts I will have in between.
(He plans thoroughly for all three meals and the desserts.)
He has been having to take off his shirt...
for the shows he's in.
- Right. - I see.
Even for "Would You Marry Me?," I had to be topless in a scene.
I had to constantly be on a diet.
I felt desperate as I was done with the project.
Us celebrities...
have to suffer so much when we have to be topless.
(Ta-da!)
(I know how you feel, Bum June.)
(He added a lot of cheese without thinking about being topless.)
(The leftover cheese is closed up in a zipper bag.)
He's really neat.
(It's neatly kept in the fridge.)
(Taking out)
(The bread gets toasted in the meanwhile.)
(Crunchy)
(He opens up the bread with scissors.)
(Cheddar cheese is placed inside.)
(His mouth is already watering.)
It looks amazing.
(The gold cheese becomes one with the bulgogi.)
- Gosh! - That looks delicious.
That looks delicious.
That's like a bulgogi burger.
He might gain a lot of weight.
- Gosh! - I used low-sugar bulgogi.
I used allulose instead of sugar.
- We all love allulose. - Right.
Even the bread is low on sugar.
It has less than a bowl of rice of calories.
(Fascinated)
Why are you so obsessed with low-sugar food?
It's the least I can do to keep my conscience.
I understand.
But won't it become massive when everything is gathered?
When low-sugar foods come together, they become high-sugar food.
(That's a great way to put it!)
(He made the cheese bulgogi sandwich in a flash.)
(Opening)
They're all low-sugar sauces.
Ten low-sugar items add up to become high in sugar.
(He has various types of sauces.)
(Along with low-sugar and low-calorie sauces,)
(his half-cheat day breakfast is ready.)
I'll start eating now.
He's eating really early.
(Pressing the remote control)
Starting from now...
(He starts eating after turning on the TV.)
What is that?
That is the garlic dipping sauce.
Gosh.
I wanted it to be tasty,
but I had to think about my health as well.
Gosh, you're eating so well.
Gosh!
It's insane.
Monde.
I'm so happy right now.
This time, it's the low-sugar chipotle sauce.
There's a low-sugar chipotle sauce?
There's even a low-sugar Bburinkle sauce.
Right.
That's crazy.
(His feet bounce up and down in joy.)
So that was what I did.
(Focused)
That looks really good.
- I love doing that as well! - Right?
- Gosh! - Watching food videos.
You're watching pastry videos that early in the morning?
(It's currently 6:50am.)
- Right. - Gosh.
- You must really like bread. - I love bread.
(Bread instead of rice for breakfast)
(Putting in his mouth)
That must feel so dry. You must have some soup.
- We're the ones who prefer rice. - Right.
There should be an onion soup, at least.
- Gosh, an onion soup. - Right.
There must be low-sugar onion soups as well.
- Right. - Low-sugar onion soups?
I'm sure you can find them.
I've seen up to low-sugar kkanpunggis.
- Gosh. - That's the winner.
It's that one, isn't it? The one with Seongsu-dong in its name.
Yes! You're right!
I eat that often.
- It's good. - It's actually a thing?
- Yes. - It wasn't a joke?
There's everything you can imagine.
Low-sugar kkanpunggi, low-sugar yukgaejang,
low-sugar tangsuyuk, and low-sugar jokbal.
- What? - Right.
There's even low-sugar chicken feet.
- Gosh. - No way.
Are there no low-sugar phones?
- I'm pretty sure you can find them. - No low-sugar laptops?
The screen brightness is quite low for those phones.
There are even low-sugar nuggets.
- Gosh! - They taste just the same.
Gosh, why does that word annoy me so much? "Low-sugar."
It feels just as annoying as the Fun Run.
- So that was what it felt like. - He overcame himself.
You learned what it felt like today.
(The low-sugar food lover finished his meal well.)
(Rushing over)
(He washes the dishes right away after eating.)
(Wiping)
(He cleans up right away as well.)
- Gosh. - He's really neat.
(He opens the freezer this time.)
(He gets something out from the freezer.)
- Is he eating again? - It's bread.
This guy is amazing.
He must really love bread.
(It heads into the air fryer to get heated up.)
(Thinking)
(He gets something else out from the freezer.)
- What is that? Ice cream? - Tofu?
(Is that for me?)
Ice cream.
- Is it bread again? - Bread again?
(More bread appears.)
(He eats another type of bread while heating up the bread.)
That one looks good.
It's really good.
Do you know White Windmill?
- Of course, I do! - You do?
People wait in long lines for that.
- Right. - What is that?
Is that a low-sugar windmill?
No.
It's not?
It sounds like it will turn really slowly.
- That must be frustrating. - That must be frustrating.
(Give me some as well.)
I'm sorry, Monde.
You little rascal.
After I finish this, I'll bring out your favorite.
How adorable.
(It's ready.)
(He has his 3rd type of bread at 7:05am.)
- Gosh. - It's a croissant.
- It looks like... - What is that?
That's the 10,000-layer croissant.
You can add cream to it as well.
Is it fresh cream or cream cheese?
I added fresh cream, custard cream, and vanilla beans.
- Okay. So that's what it's like. - Right.
(Crunchy)
(It's so good.)
Actually, I'm a big bread lover.
Ever since I was young, my mother...
brought home this much bread.
She bought all kinds of bread and cut them all up.
I finished all of them in a single day.
I think that was when...
I started liking bread.
(Licking his lips)
- It's filled with bread. - It's my bread freezer.
It's all bread.
This is insane.
It's so good.
I should order some more.
(Choose your order.)
What is that?
- I ordered more. - You're ordering more?
Were you possessed by a ghost that died while craving bread?
People who love bread...
go on a bread pilgrimage.
They go on trips to places where there are bakeries.
- Right. - Bread pilgrimage?
- Bread pilgrimage? - I go on bread pilgrimages.
There's the Bread Taxi...
- and Bread Bus in Daejeon. - Bread Bus?
Because of Sungsimdang?
They go to the top bakeries in Daejeon.
- Gosh. - There's a unique world for that.
Right.
(The third type of bread disappears in a flash.)
(The fourth type of bread appears.)
More?
You must know this. It's the condensed milk baguette...
and cheese baguette.
(This time, he'll have salty types of bread.)
- Does it not feel greasy? - No.
He must handle greasy food well.
I'm seeing all kinds of bread I've never seen before.
I've never seen those as well.
- That's Emmental cheese. - That looks amazing!
You've given up on low-sugar food all of sudden.
He had low-sugar food...
- to have all of the bread. - Right!
- That will definitely be fattening. - It's his cheat day.
It was my half-cheat day.
What did you have when you were on a diet?
There's a bread that's made of protein.
- Protein bread? - Right. That's a thing.
Protein bread?
- So. - There are protein chocolate pies.
I couldn't give up on having bread.
(Crunchy)
(Satisfied)
(He moves around as it's delicious.)
That must be the best one.
Gosh, I want some.
I love Emmental bagels as well.
As I had something salty, I'll have something sweet.
I want some kimchi jjigae just after watching this.
- Gosh, that looks good too. - Is that garlic bread?
That's the cheddar cheese baguette.
He's having more cheese than a European.
He ate bread for an hour.
(He cleans up again.)
(I'm done with the cleaning.)
(He washes the dishrag right away as well.)
That's neat.
(An exercise bike?)
(He even gets changed.)
(He starts exercising right after having breakfast at 8am.)
Doesn't the food come up...
if you ride that right after eating?
I used the exercise bike every single day.
I've tried using it before my meals and after my meals.
It suited me better to use it after meals.
It felt like it burned and digested away...
the food that I had.
(It has been 6 minutes since he started pedaling.)
(Sweating)
- He sweats a lot. - His sweating is coming out.
(He wraps his head with the towel...)
(and starts pedaling even faster.)
- There's the cheese coming out. - Cheese?
That was the cream just now.
The Emmental cheese.
(He moves his body to digest the bread he had.)
(Dripping)
(Grunting)
(This morning...)
That's tough to do.
I can't do that.
Gosh.
- How many calories is that? - Around 175?
(Picking up)
Don't tell me he's ordering bread.
An order for bread.
- Seo Bum June! - What are you up to, Grandma?
- It's your grandmother? - Yes.
I was taking out the trash to prepare to move out.
I should've gone to help you.
Gosh, you're too busy. Why bother?
I'm not busy.
- Grandma. - Yes?
After moving into the new house and getting things sorted,
you have to take a picture with me as you promised to.
- Sure. - She has a great grandson.
- Okay. - All right.
I love you, Grandma.
- I love you too. - I miss my grandmother!
Bye.
(He carried on with his exercise with his grandmother's support.)
(I've given it my all.)
Done.
(He completes his 51-minute morning exercise.)
Gosh, look at how his back is drenched.
It's great to sweat in the morning.
- Right. - It must feel relieving.
(He takes a refreshing shower after sweating.)
I'll be back.
Where is he going this early?
He left the house at 9am.
Let's go.
Where could he be going?
Isn't it a department store?
It feels like a shopping center.
Where is this?
- It's a bakery. - Are you serious?
- Seriously? - No way!
(Injeolmi butter, peanut butter chocolate chip bar)
(The counter is filled with various types of desserts.)
(Bum June heads straight to the kitchen.)
- What? - You run a bakery?
(Chuckling)
(He heads to the kitchen right after entering.)
- What? - You run a bakery?
It must be so that he can have a lot of bread.
Is that why he works at a bakery?
- As a part-timer? - Yes.
You must be paid with bread.
(He starts the coffee machine like a skilled part-timer.)
(He makes two cups of iced Americano in a flash.)
- Gosh. - Who is that?
It's the owner.
- Hey, sis. - Yes?
I'll help you now. Tell me what to do.
This is the dessert cafe...
that my older sister runs.
- I see. - I see.
At times, during my days off,
I work as a part-timer at my sister's store.
I was told there was a big order for 700 butter bars.
- An order for 700 butter bars? - That was why I came to help.
So those are butter bars?
They're soft.
Each box must have 74 butter bars.
There are 74 in 1? Okay.
You can start with this.
(I got it.)
(Focused)
(The basket is emptied in no time.)
- Another box. - Okay.
Is she making the butter bars back there?
Yes. She kept making them.
(The younger brother focuses on packaging them.)
It looks like he has done this many times before.
Wait for me.
(Another box is filled in a short period of time.)
It's quite heavy.
It shows that he has worked as a part-timer for quite some time.
- He knows how to work. - He knows how to work.
Deal with the order as well.
The order?
(Walking over)
(He checks the order right away.)
Vanilla pound.
Strawberry butter bar.
(He finds the desserts skillfully.)
(Stooping)
(Scribbling)
(He writes the note himself this time.)
Gosh, his handwriting is so nice.
Your handwriting makes my heart flutter.
It's like that of a high school girl.
You see that kind of handwriting from the notebook of a girl...
who receives good grades.
- That... - Those who write diaries well.
If a note with that handwriting is stuck on a canned coffee...
and placed on my desk...
"What is this?"
But it'd say, "Please keep quiet."
(Breaking the fantasy)
Bum June would've written it.
(Please keep quiet.)
(Writing a note that shook Kian84's heart)
(Sticking it on the bag)
(Focused)
Gosh, he's good.
Goodness, he's meticulous.
(A one-day partner who does his job skillfully)
I've worked part time at a cafe...
and a bar.
I've even worked part time at an internet cafe too.
While working part time,
- I saw Yoo Ji Tae. - I think I saw that video.
I think I was 20 then.
- I actually saw this. - What is this?
- What is this? - What is it?
(9 years ago, Bum June was working part time,)
(dreaming of becoming an actor.)
(Hi, Bum June.)
(His role model Yoo Ji Tae visited him at his part time work.)
(Teary-eyed)
I'm Yoo Ji Tae.
This itself looks like a drama.
I know. It looks like a setup, right?
I heard that they were filming a documentary...
about people who do many part-time jobs.
- The crew lied to you. - Yes.
They told me it was a documentary.
To root for a student who dreams of becoming an actor,
Ji Tae went there.
- Really? - Because his role model was Ji Tae.
- Oh, from that channel? - Yes.
There was a lot of similar content back then.
- It must've been really moving. - It must've been really moving.
(Take a seat.)
(Let's have a beer together.)
- I heard you studied acting. - Yes.
(I came to see you.)
(Yoo Ji Tae gave heartfelt advice without holding back.)
I wanted to see him after that,
and I saw him at a movie premier.
- After you made it? - Yes.
I said hello to him then,
- and he remembered me. - Of course.
- Of course he remembers. - We exchanged our numbers then.
I still keep in touch with him.
- I see. - He's like a savior.
Why was Yoo Ji Tae your role model among many actors?
I came to like him after seeing one of his interviews.
Like the things he told me.
When I heard that in person...
Even now, I get emotional thinking about it.
(He becomes emotional even now.)
I don't think I can even talk to him.
My goodness.
- I see. - My gosh.
(A 20-year-old young man who dreamed of becoming an actor...)
(grew into an actor who won all the Best Rookie Awards.)
I was really happy, and it was a really precious moment.
It must've motivated you big time.
- Hey. I'll take the order. - Okay.
(Packing for the delivery orders skillfully)
One yellow cheese pudding and one yellow cheese crumble?
I'll leave the two cups of coffee here.
Your sister must trust you a lot and leave it to you.
Of course. It's the best...
- when your family works for you. - Mission clear.
(Packing even the last box neatly)
(Same-day delivery, fresh food)
Gosh, 700 butter bars?
(They finally finished packing 700 butter bars.)
You're the best.
Great job. Thank you so much.
- Are we done? - Yes, we are.
We are?
I'll take one apple banana strawberry crumble.
Apple banana strawberry crumble sounds good.
One pumpkin pie.
(One pumpkin pie, please.)
(Picking as much bread as he can to satisfy a sweet craving)
It's salt and butter.
He loves bread so much.
It was urgent, and you helped me today,
so I'll give them to you for free.
Because I love bread, she gives me bread...
for my labor.
- For your labor? - Yes.
For your sister, there won't be any leftover bread.
- It'd be nice. - She'd be grateful.
Because it's iffy to sell it if there's only one day left...
until the expiration date.
- They throw away all the leftovers. - Yes.
- You're such a nice brother. - Of course.
- It's really nice. - She gets to clear the leftovers...
- and save money for your labor. - She doesn't have to throw them.
I hope my brother who's in Gwangju watches this.
You should heat it up before eating it.
- It looks so good. It's insane. - You should heat it up.
- On top of this... You know, right? - He's so sweet.
Add that.
- Okay. - A brother does that?
This is impossible.
Thanks for this.
- Thank you for the food too. - Thank you.
I'll get going.
- Bye. - This is so lovely to watch.
Great work today.
He'll get even closer to her as he gets older.
There are siblings like them.
(Thanks to his sister, he packed lots of bread.)
(Going back home where Monde is waiting)
Monde.
Monde, you waited for me?
Gosh, he must've waited for you.
Goodness.
You're so cute.
- Monde, you're so cute. - He wants to play with him.
Goodness. There.
I see. You missed me.
- Gosh, he was bored. - I love it.
Monde, did you miss me?
Gosh. Did you sleep well?
(Opening)
The food supply.
Bread freezer.
He eats and refills.
I should eat now too, right?
Oh, it's only 1pm.
(He naturally heads to the fridge.)
I was starving.
- It was past lunchtime. - Have some rice, please.
(Opening)
(He took out red kimchi that has aged well.)
There you go.
(In the pan coated with oil,)
(he makes scallion oil.)
I used chicken breast ham to feel less guilty.
(Then he fries spicy kimchi on top of it.)
(Pouring)
Oh, is it kimchi fried rice?
Gosh, I love that.
It looks so good.
(Focused)
What?
(Making a hole in the middle?)
- Eggs. - He must be adding eggs.
Eggs or...
It's cream. It's whipping cream.
Gosh, whipping cream?
- Is it risotto? - To that precious kimchi...
(They can't imagine the taste.)
Today, I chose kimchi fried rice.
It's cheddar, mozzarella, whipping cream kimchi fried rice.
I first saw the recipe on social media.
I was really curious how it'd taste.
(Shall I make it in earnest?)
Add mozzarella and cheddar cheese.
Then add a slice of cheddar cheese.
Then close the lid and melt them.
Then it becomes kimchi fried rice...
that's like thick and creamy risotto.
- Oh, like rose style? - Yes, like risotto.
It must be.
You must like Western food.
Yes, I like cheese and dairy products.
(It's a perfect dish for a cheese lover.)
It's done.
(Carrying the whole pot)
Goodness.
What is it?
(Kimchi fried rice that's like risotto is ready.)
(Exclaiming)
(It looks a bit unfamiliar.)
(He mixes it thoroughly.)
(Cheese stretching)
The cheese looks so good.
(Taking a bite)
(Amazed)
(Exclaiming)
(Enjoying)
This is crazy.
It tastes exactly like risotto.
It wraps the kimchi fried rice smoothly.
I'd like to try a bite.
(Stretching up high)
(Taking a big spoonful)
(Amazed)
(Scraping)
(It's super thick unlike how it was at first.)
It's like adding cheese to kimchi fried rice.
At first, the whipping cream is watery.
But toward the end, it becomes creamy and thick.
"Creamy?"
It was my first time hearing it from someone after Jang Woo.
(Jang Woo liked using the word "creamy" to describe a taste.)
(We have a new "creamy" man.)
Jang Woo's is high-sugar creamy.
- But his is low-sugar creamy. - I know.
(The fried rice became creamy after some time.)
(Exclaiming)
(It's so good that he can't stop eating.)
It's really good.
(Empty)
He eats so well.
(He finished the whole thing, not leaving a single grain.)
(That was a good meal.)
(He does the dishes right away.)
- He does the dishes right away. - He's diligent.
(Spraying)
- Oh, my. - He's so neat.
(Shining)
(Roaming around the kitchen even after his meal)
(Beeping)
He's having pastry again?
A financier?
It's what I brought from my sister's shop.
Crispy on the outside, soft on the inside.
(Placing something on top)
- Gosh. - Isn't that butter?
Yes.
(Adding butter to a financier)
My goodness.
(Excited)
(Butter and butter financier)
He added two bars.
I really can't eat cheesy food.
Financiers have lots of butter in them.
Financiers are made...
- using browned butter. - Exactly.
But if you add that butter on top of the buttered financier,
the flavor triples.
Gosh, butter?
This is crazy. It looks so good.
(Taking a bite)
(Crispy)
(Amazing taste)
Gosh.
- Gosh. - It was shocking.
You might think it's too much. Not at all.
When you take a bite, the flavor of butter...
doubles. No.
It's enriched by 10, 100, or 1,000 times.
When the salt sprinkled on top meets the butter...
- Ta-da. - "Ta-da."
(This is crazy!)
How can he look so happy?
It was really good.
(Feeling like he's on top of the world)
(He can't stop because of its crazy flavor.)
(Staring)
Gosh, I can't help but eat little by little.
You eat cheesy stuff well.
(Having the last bite while holding back his tears)
(He wants more.)
(Sighing)
(The financier disappeared in a second.)
He eats a lot.
Gosh, that was crazy.
(He can't get over it.)
(That was seriously amazing.)
(Taking the dishes he used to the sink right away)
(He does the dishes again.)
How many times do you do dishes in a day?
- You'll get hand eczema. - He'll get hand eczema.
- I know. - So I...
- Oh, my! - Goodness!
It's because he does dishes so many times.
The back of his hand is scraped. That must hurt.
(After doing dishes while overcoming hand eczema...)
(Taking his phone)
(Oh, no)
What is it?
(He suddenly goes outside?)
(Returning with a parcel)
You ordered bread again, didn't you?
It must be something else.
Please let it be live webfoot octopus.
I hope it's live shrimp.
It's in season. Or crabs.
- Or young wild radish greens. - Young wild radish greens?
Please, I beg you!
(A mysterious box containing fresh food)
What is it?
- No way. - What is it?
It's bread.
I knew it'd be bread...
because if it's food,
- they'd wrap it one more time. - That's right.
What is this?
I did booking for bread,
and they send it in order.
It's really hard.
- Exactly. - You call it booking for bread?
- Booking for bread. - Yes.
Easily put,
it's like booking a ticket for a concert.
Like booking a ticket for a concert.
To get the famous bread from the bakery...
- Right. - Like booking a ticket...
for your seat at a concert,
you book for your bread.
Then you can put it in your cart in advance.
Really?
(To the bread with zipper bags instead of a dish)
(Putting it in)
(Carefully packing the delivered bread one by one)
I've never seen anyone portioning bread.
When the bread gets delivered,
I'd cut it a little and eat some freshly that day.
Then I'd wrap them...
What does eating freshly mean?
You call it eating freshly...
when you eat the bread as soon as it's delivered.
- Like fresh fish? - It's fresh fish bread.
- It's fresh bread. - Fresh bread?
If you freeze it, you call it eating the frozen.
- Eating the frozen. - Eating freshly.
Eating freshly and eating the frozen.
Heating it up in an air fryer.
Heating it up in an air fryer. That's when you use an air fryer?
Eating the frozen after heating it up in an air fryer.
You know it, right?
You can't eat right away after heating it up in an air fryer.
- You need to cool it down. - Oh, it needs to be cooled down.
- That's right. - After heating it up, cool it down.
After heating it up in an air fryer, you sigh.
- No, not sighing. Cool it down. - Cool it down.
After heating it up in an air fryer, cool it down.
- "Sighing?" - Not sighing.
What are you talking about?
I have no idea what he's saying.
- For some bread... - It's even harder than Japanese.
- Gosh, I'm dizzy. - After heating it up...
- They have... - What does that mean?
a harder time communicating than when Lingard was here.
Honestly, I was already dizzy when he mentioned booking bread.
(Feeling a language barrier even though it's Korean)
- King Sejong the Great... - King Sejong the Great...
would roll over in his grave.
- I'm sorry. - King Sejong the Great...
- would understand it now. - He'd make a lightning strike.
Is this eating freshly or after using an air fryer?
I freeze it right away and heat it up in an air fryer.
Freeze and heat it up in an air fryer.
Heating it up in an air fryer after freezing it.
(I'll freeze it first.)
(Storing it carefully in his bread storage)
Gosh, it's full.
Gosh, bread is my life.
(A time that nourished both his body and soul)
(Breathing hard)
(Panting)
- Again? - He's riding it again?
(Since I ate, I should exercise!)
Because I ate...
(Whipping cream kimchi fried rice, 10 minutes)
(Butter financier, 10 minutes)
Having delicious bread beats hard training.
You're right.
(Since he enjoyed it, he doesn't stop exercising.)
I saw him riding it up to four hours.
- That? - Really?
- Because you like bread so much? - Yes.
Because I ride it for too long every day,
the saddle...
- It collapsed? - The metal frame was exposed.
- Oh, my. - Oh, my.
Right. Just like how you need to change the saddle...
if you ride a bicycle for too long.
(The food saved for the future exercises)
(He's happy on his cheat day.)
It's amazing that he's determined to eat...
- Right. - by working out like that.
(Panting)
Done.
(I burned up all the calories from bread.)
He completed 50 minutes.
(He showers refreshingly after sweating.)
Monde. Shall we go for a walk?
Shall we go for a walk together?
Monde, let's go.
Maybe he's using that as an excuse to go to a bakery.
No way.
I won't let him be.
The weather is amazing.
(Taking light steps to somewhere)
We're here.
- Wait. Isn't that a market? - He's going to a market.
(Jayang Traditional Market)
(He arrived at a traditional market.)
Aren't you going to a bakery that's open 24 hours?
They must have other things.
Yes, let's have sundae.
- Or dumplings. - Yes.
Tteokbokki sounds good too.
(Surprised)
Actually, they have Korean-style bread too.
- They do. - They do, like sulbbang.
Monde, there are rice cake bars.
- Goodness. - A rice cake place?
Slice chicken feet jelly?
Monde.
There are so many delicious things.
They only have the top-tier yellowtail.
- Gosh, yellowtail. - Yellowtails are in season.
It's in full swing.
Hello.
Maybe they have yellowtail bread.
Is it okay to bring a dog inside?
Can you pack a small serving of yellowtail?
- You'd like a small serving? - Yes.
"Would You Marry Me?"
(The market is in love with his drama, "Would You Marry Me?")
Hello.
- I'm a big fan! - Thank you.
I'll drop by somewhere first and pick it up later.
- Can I take a photo with you? - Sure.
I saw you on TV until yesterday.
One, two.
He's popular in the market.
(Having an on-the-spot fan meet before realizing it)
- Thank you. - Sure.
So many people must've watched your drama.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- I'm enjoying your drama. - Thank you.
- "Would You Marry Me?" - Right.
Gosh, who was it again?
- From "Would You Marry Me?" - Yes.
(Spotting something after the fan meet)
Hello, sir.
Sir, I'd like to pack four pieces of tteokgalbi.
- Four? - Tteokgalbi sounds good.
Gosh, I really want to eat that.
- Thank you. Have a good one. - Bye.
I'll take a cup of plain flavor.
He eats so well.
You like to spread out various food.
- That's right. - That's when you're the happiest.
Ma'am, I'll take a plate of baby crab.
That's delicious. I like that.
You just pressed it?
Gosh, thank you.
(He picks up the packed yellowtail.)
Monde, let's go now.
(He returns home with both hands full.)
(He got a lot of things.)
(Washing his hands thoroughly as soon as he comes home)
(He gets ready to eat.)
Goodness.
My gosh.
(Putting the fritters together)
This is crazy.
- Yellowtail looks crazy good. - Gosh, that looks delicious.
He cut it thick.
You need to cut yellowtail thick.
(Putting the vegetables and white kimchi neatly on a dish)
That's what makes you happy. Spreading food and eating it.
That's why you work hard.
(A table filled with food from the traditional market)
Isn't that too much to eat by yourself?
I held back a lot while I was on a diet.
Monde.
(Lights off)
He's setting the mood.
That's when I'm the happiest.
Thank you for the food.
(Solemn)
For the first bite...
(Salivating)
The yellowtail looks good.
(Taking a piece of thick yellowtail)
(Dipping it in salt...)
(then in sesame oil)
The yellowtail from that store was really good.
(Smiling)
I love it.
It's therapeutic for me to see you not having bread.
Since I'm having yellowtail by myself...
He's having two pieces at once.
- Add aged kimchi on top. - Aged kimchi sounds good.
This adds a kick to it. And add sesame oil.
(Adding pickled chili and wasabi that'll make it less greasy)
My goodness. Yellowtail.
That combination is really good.
- I know. - I love it.
You should have a fully grown yellowtail.
(A taste that makes you laugh)
(Getting up)
(Opening the fridge in the middle of his meal)
(Adding a huge ice cube)
- That's it. - Take your time.
- Do you drink too? - I love it.
(Filling the cool iced cup)
It looks like you're at an izakaya.
- That's right. - You should finish it in two sips.
The small glass won't do.
- Let all the organs feel it. - I know.
You finally talk now that he's having soju.
(Gulping)
Your health is okay, right? Is your cholesterol level okay?
Yes, I have clean blood.
I work out as much as I eat.
You must work out hard.
- I really love that. - I know.
(Crunchy)
(Frowning as it's so good)
Thanks to today, I think I can keep going forward.
I got to think that it's good to eat...
when my body craves it. I think it's good for my body.
You hold back your desires to eat on other days.
I need to watch my figure my whole life.
Because I want to be an actor all my life,
I need to have a healthy mentality...
and eat when I want to.
Then I'll move around more.
I think this kind of mindset is important.
It's so good.
(The cheat day he hasn't had for a while is ending.)
- What is this? - Bread again?
(Amazed)
What is that?
- What is that? - It's cheese on carp bread.
- No, I mean butter. - Butter on carp bread.
It was really good.
Gosh.
Then he'll ride the indoor bike again.
He should.
(Cheat Day Filled with Happiness is Over)
(Next story)
(Feeling nervous amid the murmuring)
(Hyun Moo is standing in the middle of it.)
(It's a wedding hall?)
(May I ask you to officiate my wedding?)
(Officiate a wedding when I'm not married?)
(Kian84 will host the wedding.)
(Moomoo will officiate the wedding.)
(Soon to debut as an officiator)
(Stammering)
(Can you host it if I fail to?)
(I'm serious.)
(I'm in no position to help.)
(The wedding hall is packed with people,)
(making him even more nervous.)
(Jang Woo)
(Finally meeting the star of the day)
(Hyun Moo, I'm counting on you.)
(Host84 is heading to the stage.)
(Where does an officiator sit?)
(It's my first time officiating. Will I be able to do well?)
(This is nothing.)
(Yes, Hyun Moo. Let's do this.)
(Soon, the wedding begins.)
(Please welcome Mr. Jun Hyun Moo...)
(with a round of applause.)
(He's the star of the wedding.)
(Groom Lee Jang Woo...)
(enters.)
(Here comes Jang Woo.)
(He must be nervous. Oh, gosh.)
(The Rainbow Club members are nervous as well.)
(Palm Oil Prince Jang Woo is about to say goodbye.)
(Goodbye will hurt us, but it'll be graceful)
(The graduation of Palm Oil Prince who's been on the show for 6 years)
(A Beautiful Goodbye)
(Boom)
(Keeping the beat energetically)
(It's Dowoon?)
(It's been a while.)
(I'm Drummer Yoon Dowoon of DAY6.)
(He left early in the morning for the sea to fish.)
(An undisputed fishing genius)
(Today, he's humming at home.)
(Shall I show off my skills?)
(I haven't cooked in a while.)
(Skillful)
(I guess I'm a genius cook too.)
(What is this?)
(It's not what I had in mind.)
(Gosh, it's hot!)
(Clumsy)
(I guess I'm not a genius cook.)
(Sniffing)
(The place he has arrived to soothe his distressed heart)
(A music club)
(Enter the world of jazz.)
(The mood is free...)
(and sensual.)
That's cool too.
(Having a good time at a place he likes)
(It's twice as fun as he's with his friends.)
(Right then, a jam session starts.)
(Improvising and performing music spontaneously)
(Nervous)
(Shall we give it a try?)
(Fly to the Dowoon)